oddsportal.com 2017-06-15

# Odds Portal: Privacy Policy

Provider of OddsPortal.com respects the privacy of visitors to OddsPortal.com ("Site"). We are committed to protecting your privacy online. We use information we collect about you to provide you with the services which you may access through our web site. We understand that you do not want the personal information you provide to us distributed indiscriminately and here we inform you how we collect information, what we do with it, who has access to it and what controls you have over its use.

**Collection of Personal Information**  
We do not collect any personal information where you simply browse our website. Nevertheless, we may, upon registration or at other times, ask you to submit some information about you, such as your e-mail address. You are under no obligation to provide us with this information. However, if you should choose to withhold requested information, we may not be able to provide you the services required.

**Use of Information**  
We will use the information you provide to us especially for the following purposes:  
\- Communicate with you.  
\- Send you forgotten password to your personal account.  
\- Send you information we think you may find useful, including our products, services information and commercial / advertising materials.  
\- Provide advanced services.  
\- Improve the content of our web page.  
\- Provide you with personalized page content and/or layout.

**Disclosure of Information**  
We do not sell, trade or rent your information provided to us to others. We can however transfer this information to other subject in case of sale of the Site. We may need to disclose your provided information to third parties where this is required by law or where this is necessary for the function of a service provided to you. We may provide statistics about visitors, sales, traffic, etc. to third party vendors but these will not include any identifying information. Users who don't wish to receive our emails anymore can unsubscribe by writing to Site provider via contact form.

**Log Files**  
When you visit our Site, we automatically log your IP address and pages visited. It help us administer the Site and to collect broad demographic information for aggregate use.

**Cookie Disclaimer**  
A "cookie" is information stored on your computer by a web server and used to customize your web service in some way. OddsPortal.com Site uses cookies to store information about your interactions that may be needed later to perform a function. You can choose not to accept cookies and still use our services. However, you can be unable to use the cookie-dependent features. Refer to the help information in your browser software for instructions on how to disable cookies.

**Your Acceptance of The Terms**  
You consent to our collection and use of information and to the use of that information in accordance with the privacy policy set out above. If we change our privacy policy in any way, we will post these changes on this page. You should check these terms on frequent basis.

**Provider Information**  
OddsPortal.com is provided by:

LiveSport Media Ltd  
CMS House First Floor, St. Peter’s Street  
San Gwann SGN 2310, Malta  
Company ID: C 54555
